Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Sweet Secrets=
=أسرار حلوة=
=Episode 18= (Terror In The Train Car)
=الحلقة 18= (الرعب في عربة القطار)
Mr. Jing.
السيد جينغ.
This bottle of red wine was specially prepared for you.
لقد تم إعداد هذه الزجاجة من النبيذ الأحمر خصيصًا لك.
It's rich and mellow in flavor.
إنه غني ولطيف في النكهة.
I hope you like it.
أتمنى أن يعجبك.
Even the worst wine in my cellar
حتى أسوأ أنواع النبيذ في قبوي
is a hundred times better than this.
أفضل من هذا بمئة مرة.
Naturally, this bottle of wine
بطبيعة الحال، هذه الزجاجة من النبيذ
can't compare to your treasures.
لا يمكن مقارنتها بكنوزك.
But what I'm offering isn't wine.
ولكن ما أقدمه ليس نبيذًا.
It's sincerity.
إنها الصدق.
Mr. Jing.
السيد جينغ.
Give it another try.
حاول مرة أخرى.
Find out what it tastes like.
اكتشف ما هو مذاقه.
Your alluring manner.
طريقتك الجذابة.
In my eyes,
في عيني،
it's just like this wine.
إنه مثل هذا النبيذ تمامًا.
It's both cheap and shameless.
إنه رخيص ووقح.
Do you prefer
هل تفضل؟
domineering, forceful women?
نساء متسلطات وقويات؟
I have many sides, you know.
لدي جوانب عديدة، كما تعلم.
A hidden gem of a girl.
جوهرة مخفية للفتاة.
No domineering, forceful women
لا للنساء المسيطرات والقويات
have ever left this room alive.
هل غادرت هذه الغرفة على قيد الحياة؟
Since boldness and dominance won't work on you,
لأن الجرأة والهيمنة لن تنجح معك،
I can be gentle and sweet instead.
أستطيع أن أكون لطيفًا وحلوًا بدلًا من ذلك.
Miss Gu, do you have a fever?
آنسة جو، هل تعانين من الحمى؟
If you've gone mad,
إذا كنت قد جننت،
go see a doctor.
اذهب لرؤية الطبيب.
A fever?
حمى؟
You know I hate the smell of humans the most.
أنت تعلم أنني أكره رائحة البشر أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
But still, thank you for giving me a helper.
لكن مع ذلك، أشكرك على إعطائي مساعدًا.
She traded something that interests me.
لقد تداولت شيئًا يثير اهتمامي.
It's been a fair exchange.
لقد كان تبادلا عادلا.
I was pleased.
لقد كنت سعيدا.
Is the sword
هل السيف
fixed?
مُثَبَّت؟
You really used up all your spiritual power.
لقد استنفدت كل قوتك الروحية حقًا.
Give me the sword
أعطني السيف
and I won't let you down.
ولن أخذلك.
You two have fought since childhood.
لقد كنتما تتقاتلان منذ الطفولة.
Judging by how serious you are,
استنادا إلى مدى جديتك،
I bet you're harboring some ulterior motive.
أراهن أنك تخفي دوافع خفية.
Are you afraid that I'll kill Li Motong
هل أنت خائف من أن أقتل لي موتونغ؟
with this sword
مع هذا السيف
and become the new Lord of Wujian?
ويصبح اللورد الجديد لـWujian؟
I haven't changed my mind.
لم أغير رأيي.
Don't forget,
لا تنسى،
you belong to Wujian.
أنت تنتمي إلى Wujian.
Thank you,
شكرًا لك،
Supreme Priest.
الكاهن الأعظم.
Yan, long time no see.
يان، لم نلتقي منذ وقت طويل.
Only Lan could bring you back.
فقط لان يمكن أن يعيدك.
We tried to do so, and you never showed up.
لقد حاولنا القيام بذلك، ولكنك لم تظهر أبدًا.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
You've forgotten us after getting into a relationship.
لقد نسيتنا بعد أن دخلت في علاقة.
We're all good sisters.
نحن جميعا أخوات جيدات.
Since Lan asked,
منذ أن سألت لان،
of course I have to be here.
بالطبع يجب أن أكون هنا.
Go ahead with your rehearsal.
إستمر ​​في التدريب الخاص بك.
I'll join you in a bit.
سوف أنضم إليكم قليلا.
See you later.
أراك لاحقًا.
We meet again.
نلتقي مرة أخرى.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Miss Lu.
السيدة لو.
Don't think I can no longer kill you
لا أعتقد أنني لم أعد أستطيع قتلك
just because you missed the night of Crimson Moon.
فقط لأنك فاتتك ليلة القمر القرمزي.
The Soul-Eating Sword has been restored.
لقد تم استعادة سيف أكل الروح.
I can take the Mei pearl today.
أستطيع أن آخذ لؤلؤة مي اليوم.
I guess you're not doing it
أعتقد أنك لا تفعل ذلك
for Li Motong.
للي موتونغ.
You just want it for yourself.
تريد ذلك لنفسك فقط.
So what if you've got that right?
فماذا لو كنت على حق في هذا الأمر؟
In the end,
في النهاية،
you'll still die by my sword.
سوف تموت بسيفى على كل حال.
You hurt Li Motong,
لقد آذيت لي موتونغ،
and now you want my life too?
والآن تريد حياتي أيضًا؟
I won't let you have your way!
لن أسمح لك بالحصول على طريقتك!
You and your futile struggle.
أنت ونضالك العقيم.
Do you think you can escape?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع الهروب؟
Where do you think you're going, Lu Huayan?
إلى أين تعتقد أنك ذاهب، لو هوايان؟
You can't run now.
لا يمكنك الركض الآن.
Li Motong.
لي موتونج.
You didn't take the pearl
لم تأخذ اللؤلؤة
on the night of Crimson Moon.
في ليلة القمر القرمزي.
Now you've lost the Wujian force.
لقد فقدت الآن قوة Wujian.
You've truly brought this on yourself.
لقد جلبت هذا على نفسك حقا.
Don't you dare touch her!
لا تجرؤ على لمسها!
What can you do about it?
ماذا يمكنك أن تفعل حيال ذلك؟
Li Motong!
لي موتونغ!
Get up.
استيقظ.
Keep fighting.
استمر في القتال.
(As long as I am the Lord of Wujian,)
(طالما أنا سيد ووجيان)
(you will submit to me.)
(سوف تخضع لي.)
(You've overestimated yourself!)
(لقد بالغت في تقدير نفسك!)
Li Motong!
لي موتونغ!
(How devoted you are.)
(كم أنت مخلص.)
(Have you forgotten?)
( هل نسيت ؟ )
(I'm about to become)
(أنا على وشك أن أصبح)
(the new ruler of Wujian.)
(الحاكم الجديد لووجيان.)
Don't think that I won't kill you
لا تظن أنني لن أقتلك
just because you're my brother.
فقط لأنك أخي.
Look at how pathetic you are. It's all because of this woman.
انظر إلى حالتك المزرية. كل هذا بسبب هذه المرأة.
You're not fit to be the Lord of Wujian.
أنت لست لائقًا لتكون سيد Wujian.
Jing Haisi.
جينغ هايسي.
Even if I die today,
حتى لو مت اليوم،
I won't let you lay a finger on her.
لن أسمح لك بوضع إصبعك عليها.
Fine, then.
حسنا إذن.
I'll send you both to hell.
سأرسلكما إلى الجحيم.
I never planned to give you the Mei pearl anyway.
لم أخطط أبدًا أن أقدم لك لؤلؤة مي على أي حال.
Once I have both the Chi and Mei pearls,
بمجرد حصولي على كل من لؤلؤتي تشي ومي،
I shall be the new ruler of Wujian.
سأكون الحاكم الجديد لـWujian.
The Soul-Eating Sword?
السيف آكل الروح؟
You Zimei.
أنت زيمي.
You actually restored it.
لقد قمت بإستعادته فعليا.
Yan, what are you doing?
يان ماذا تفعل؟
Who said only you could protect me?
من قال أنك وحدك القادر على حمايتي؟
The bride of Wujian must protect her king too.
ويجب على عروس ووجيان أن تحمي ملكها أيضًا.
Yan...
أنت...
To die together with the one I love,
أن أموت مع من أحب،
I'm not afraid at all.
أنا لست خائفة على الإطلاق.
I hate how devoted you lovers look.
أنا أكره كيف تبدو عشاقكم مخلصين.
It's the power of the Mei pearl.
إنها قوة لؤلؤة مي.
Yan...
أنت...
Die!
ال!
The Mei pearl...
لؤلؤة مي...
Yan...
أنت...
Yan!
الذي - التي!
(You actually activated the pearl's energy.)
(لقد قمت فعليا بتفعيل طاقة اللؤلؤة.)
(Yan.)
(شاب)
(It's all my fault.)
(كل هذا خطئي.)
(I failed to protect you.)
(لقد فشلت في حمايتك.)
♪Her long hair with the dark night♪
♪شعرها الطويل مع الليل المظلم♪
♪Looks so pure in the lamplight♪
♪يبدو نقيًا جدًا في ضوء المصباح♪
♪Blurred flesh and tears♪
♪لحم مشوش ودموع♪
♪The evil spirit's hand pushes her into a kiss upon the rail♪
♪يد الروح الشريرة تدفعها إلى قبلة على السور♪
♪Where does the truth pretend to sleep?♪
♪أين تتظاهر الحقيقة بالنوم؟♪
♪Perfect last words confront what cannot be faced♪
♪الكلمات الأخيرة المثالية تواجه ما لا يمكن مواجهته♪
♪The scent corroded by the dawn♪
♪الرائحة المتآكلة بالفجر♪
♪Is her hollow soul tossed within a bottle♪
♪هل روحها المجوفة ملقاة داخل زجاجة♪
♪Bloodless lips bloom into bright petals♪
♪شفاه بلا دم تتفتح في بتلات مشرقة♪
♪Whispering their filthy confession♪
♪همس اعترافهم القذر♪
♪A white cat intently licks the thick sweet scent of blood♪
♪قطة بيضاء تلعق باهتمام رائحة الدم الحلوة الكثيفة♪
♪Accusing, demanding♪
♪متهم، متطلب♪
♪Who are you, who am I?♪
♪من أنت، من أنا؟♪
♪How did everything turn against itself?♪
♪كيف انقلب كل شيء ضد نفسه؟♪
♪What is striking inside the cold coffin?♪
♪ما هو الملفت للنظر داخل التابوت البارد؟♪
♪The restless bones beneath♪
♪العظام المضطربة في الأسفل♪
♪To which gravestone point her broken fingers♪
♪إلى أي شاهد قبر تشير أصابعها المكسورة♪
♪Who trembles, who grieves?♪
♪من يرتجف، من يحزن؟♪
♪Who is guiltless, who bears sin?♪
♪من هو البريء، من يتحمل الخطيئة؟♪
♪Take me to unearth redemption and fearlessness♪
♪خذني إلى اكتشاف الفداء والشجاعة♪
♪He kisses her fingertips♪
♪يقبل أطراف أصابعها♪
♪Bare joints blooming white iris♪
♪المفاصل العارية تتفتح زهور السوسن البيضاء♪
♪Nightmares and roses lie asleep♪
♪الكوابيس والورود نائمة♪
♪Nothing but a date with death♪
♪لا شيء سوى موعد مع الموت♪